best mobile Insurance app now your
winner under the 2024 Assessment program
is FWD group and here we have the head
of engineering sbit mahant joining us
live sbit congratulations to you and of
course FWD Insurance over to you for a
few words thanks thanks a lot everyone
I'm honor really honored to receive the
award for the best mobile Insurance app
behalf of FWD
among so many Fantastic peers in the
industry thank you the organizers and
the jewy for selecting Omni Omni is one
of the key pillars of FWD group strategy
which makes this award more spatial
there are many bright Minds who has
contributed to this platform for last
two years but with a special mention of
Simon priston our managing director
group Co s Pand our group CTO Samuel
Tran
hermans Anan vun Shaman and the entire
team they the success of this platform
is because of these people support and
hard work the platform is very important
to us and we are fully committed to this
to bring it to the next level as it
realizes our vision to create a seamless
integrated customer Journey for all FWD
markets covering both lifestyle and
insurance policy management functions
thanks again for choosing only for this
award I think we'll see you next time
when you bring it to the next level
thank you congratulations once again uh
samit and of course to all the team in
involved in FWD Insurance best mobile
Insurance app